A Guide to the Robert Lewis Dabney Papers
University of Virginia Library
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Charles W. Dabney, 1893[?] Apr 1; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Charles W. Dabney, 1893 Apr 4; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. Uncas McCluer, 1893 Jul 13; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to his son, 1893 Jul 25; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. E. C. Gordon, 1893 Dec 12; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. J. W. Primrose, 1893 Dec 20; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Mrs. Sarah Lane, 1894 Feb 2; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to his son, 1894 Mar 23; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Charlie, 1894 Apr 2; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Mrs. Sarah Lane, 1894 Apr 14; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. S. B. Campbell, 1894 Aug 31; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. S. B. Campbell, 1894 Sep 25; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Dr. Joseph Eggleston, 1894 Oct 9; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Dr. Joseph Eggleston, 1894 Oct 29; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Miss Betty Dabney, 1894 Nov 6; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. John W. Primrose, 1894 Dec 9; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to family and friends, 1895; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Dr. Joseph Eggleston, 1895; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Dr. N. D. Hoge, 1895 Feb 20; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. P. D. Stephenson, 1895[?] Mar 24; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. S. B. Campbell, 1895 May 15; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. S. B. Campbell, 1895 Jun 2; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. Uncas McCluer, 1895 Jun 24; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. Uncas McCluer, 1895 Jul 6; APCS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Mrs. Sarah Lane, 1895 Jul 9; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. Uncas McCluer, 1895 Jul 25; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Harriet Morrison to Rev. Uncas McCluer, 1895 Jul 29; APCS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. Uncas McCluer, 1895 Aug 12; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to A. H. McCluer, 1895 Oct 4; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Mrs. Anne E. Payne, 1895 Oct 23; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Samuel A. King to Robert Lewis Dabney, 1895 Nov 4; TL [copy] (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Samuel A. King, 1895 Nov 8; TL [copy] (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. S. B. Campbell, 1895 Dec 30; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Miss Betty Dabney, 1896 Jan 4; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. J. C. Carson, 1896 Feb 22; TL [copy] (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. Uncas McCluer, 1896 Apr 28; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Charles W. Dabney, 1896 May 3; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. Uncas McCluer, 1896 May 7; APCS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. M. D. Hoge, 1896 May 16; TL (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Mrs. Anne E. Payne, 1896 Jun 16; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. Uncas McCluer, 1896 Aug 8; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. Uncas McCluer, 1896 Aug 25; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. Uncas McCluer, 1896 [?] Sep 18; APCS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Charles D. Gilkeson, 1896 Nov 29; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. Uncas McCluer, 1897 Jan 25; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to a cousin, 1897 Feb 15; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. T. W. Erwin, 1897 Mar 8; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. Samuel A. King, 1897 Mar 31; TL [copy] (Box Box 3)
- Samuel A. King, "Memorandum", 1897 Mar 31; TM (Box Box 3)
- [Robert Lewis Dabney] to his niece, 1897 Apr 9; TL (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. S. B. Campbell, 1897 Apr 10; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. S. B. Campbell, 1897 Apr 21; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to his niece, 1897 May 3; TL (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. Uncas McCluer, 1897 Jul 27; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Col. Henry Stokes, 1897 Oct 6; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. S. B. Campbell, 1897 Nov 17; ALS (Box Box 3)
- Robert Lewis Dabney to Rev. H. R. Beethe [?], 1898 Sep 20; ALS (Box Box 3)
- notes on career and death of Robert Lewis Dabney, 1895-1898; AM (Box Box 3)
- Obituaries and Letters of Condolence re: death of Robert Lewis Dabney, 1898 Jan; 26 items (Box Box 3)
- re: publication of Robert Lewis Dabney's life and letters, 1898; 18 items (Box Box 3)
- Helen [?] Dabney to Charles W. Dabney, 1898 Jan 13; ALS (Box Box 3)
- biographical sketch of Robert Lewis Dabney, 1898 Feb 5; AMS (Box Box 3)
- memorial resolution adopted by United Confederate Veterans, 1898 Feb 5; AMS (Box Box 3)
- Alexander E. Bondurant to Charles W. Dabney, 1898 Apr 11; ALS (Box Box 3)
- fragment of reminiscence about Robert Lewis Dabney at Hampden-Sidney College, 1901 Mar 21; AMs (Box Box 3)
- [to Charles W. Dabney]: material for biography of Robert Lewis Dabney, 1901; 109 items (Box Box 3)
- re: publication of Robert Lewis Dabney's life and letters, 1901-1904; 90 items (Box Box 4)
- re: publication of Robert Lewis Dabney's life and letters, 1901-1904; 46 items (Box Box 4)
- re: publication of Robert Lewis Dabney's life and letters, 1901-1904; 33 items (Box Box 4)
- misc. magazine and newspaper clippings, 1901-1917; 22 items (Box Box 4)
- Charles W. Dabney: address at Yale Bicentennial, 1902; TMs (Box Box 4)
- re: reissue of Robert Lewis Dabney's Life of Jackson, 1903; 10 TLS (Box Box 4)
- correspondence of Charles W. Dabney and Thomas C. Johnson, 1903-1916; 21 TLS, ALS (Box Box 4)
- re: Robert Lewis Dabney's Life of Jackson, 1904; 9 items (Box Box 4)
- Reviews, etc. of Thomas C. Johnson's Life and Letters of Robert Lewis Dabney, 1903-1904; 28 items (Box Box 4)
- Charles W. Dabney re: publication of Life and Letters of Robert Lewis Dabney, 1904-1910; 16 items (Box Box 4)
- Charles W. Dabney re:sketch in Library of Southern Literature, 1907-1908; 7 ALS, TLS (Box Box 4)
- Samuel B. Dabney to his brothers, 1916 Feb 10; TLS (Box Box 4)
- re: life of Robert Lewis Dabney, 1914-1930; 1 ALS, 1 TLS, 2 TL (Box Box 4)
- Thomas C. Johnson to Charles W. Dabney, 1932 Nov 23; ALS (Box Box 4)
- notebook: Robert Lewis Dabney, "Life of Jackson", n.d.; AM (Box Box 4)
- field work evaluation form: Association of Urban Universities, n.d; AD (Box Box 4)
- P. P. Claxton: "Cincinnati's Contribution to Education", n.d.; TMs (Box Box 4)
- miscellaneous clippings, papers re: autobiography of Robert Lewis Dabney, n.d. (Box Box 4)
- notebooks: Robert Lewis Dabney, autobiography, n.d.; 2 Ams (Box Box 4)
- Photostats chiefly re Thomas J. "Stonewall" Jackson (Box Box 5)
- Photostats re Thomas J. "Stonewall" Jackson (Box Box 6)